- Hey Joey,how'd the audition go? - Incredible!
乔伊，试镜结果怎么样？ 不可思议
I met the director this time and you'll never believe who it was.
我这回碰到导演了 你们绝对不会相信是谁的
- Who? - All right. I'll give you one hint.
谁呀？ 好，我给你们一个提示
Warren Beatty.
华伦比提
Yeah,there's just one thing that might be kind've a problem.
对，只是有件事 或许会成为问题
See,I,uh,had to kiss this guy.
我…必须要吻一个男人
'Cause he was just so darn cute.
因为他可爱呆了？
No,as part of the audition. See,I'm up for this part of this guy,who the main guy kisses.
不，那是试镜的一部份 我试镜的角色是 男主角要亲的男人
Well,hey. You're an actor,I say you just suck it up and do it.
你是个演员
Or you just do it.
那你就认命放嘴去吻吧
I did do it,I'm a professional.
我吻了，我很专业
Then what's the problem?
那有什么问题？
See after the scene,Mr. Beatty comes up to me and says
我试镜完之后 比提先生过来跟我说
'good actor,bad kisser'.
“好演技，烂吻技”
Can you believe that,me not a good kisser,
你们相信吗？ 我…我吻技会烂？
that's like,like Mother Theresa,not a good mother.
那就好像 好像是说 泰丽莎修女不是个好修女一样
Well,come on,who cares what that guy thinks. What does Warren Beatty know about kissing Ooh.
好了，谁在乎他怎么想 华伦比提懂什么叫做接吻？
The One With Barry And Mindy's Wedding
六人行 第2季 第24集 巴利和明蒂大喜之日
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Hey,what did your agent say?
你经纪人怎么说？
Yep,this kiss thing is defiantly a problem, Mr. Beatty wants to see it again on Monday.
接吻这回事绝对是个问题 比提先生星期一要再看一次
Man,I gotta figure out what I'm doing wrong.
我得搞清楚我哪里做错了
Oh,okay,one of you girls come over here and kiss me.
你们哪个女的先来吻我一下？
- What,forget it! - Yeah,right.
你休想 说得好
Come on,I need your help here.
不要这样嘛，我需要帮忙啊
All right. I'll do it,I kissed him before I can do it again.
我以前亲过他 我可以再亲一次
You see this,this is a friend.
看到没？这才叫朋友
Uh-huh,let's go.
开始
Oh,wait I have gum.
等等，口香糖
Okay.
Good,very good,firm but tender.
好，非常好，温柔而有力
I'd recommend you to a friend.
我会推荐给朋友
Then I don't know what it is. What's the problem?
那我就不知道问题出在哪里了
Joey,you know, maybe your just not used to kissing men,
乔伊，或许你是 不习惯亲男人罢了
maybe you just tensed up a little,
或许你只是神经紧绷了点
maybe that's what you need to work on.
也许你要克服这一点
Yeah,that makes sense.
对，有道理
Over my dead body!
除非我死了，你才可以亲我
And I'll be using his dead body as a shield.
我会用他的尸体来当挡箭牌
Come on out,honey! I'm telling you look good!
出来吧，你听我说，你很美
Tell her she looks good,tell her she looks good.
跟她说她很美…
Oh my God,
老天啊
you look so good!
你好美喔
I can not believe I have to walk down the aisle in front of 200 people
真不敢相信我得打扮得 像一瓶止吐的糖浆…
looking like something you drink when your nauseous.
…在两百人面前步上红毯
So don't,I don't see why we have to go to this thing anyway, it's your ex-fiancee's wedding.
那就别去啊 反正我不懂我们干嘛非去不可 这是你前未婚夫的婚礼
Because I promised Mindy I would.
因为我答应了明蒂
Yeah,well you promised Barry,you'd marry him.
对，你也答应过贝利 要嫁给他的
Look you guys,I have to go,I'm the Maid-of-Honor.
各位，我必须去，我是伴娘
And besides you know what I just need
我只是需要
to be in a room again with these people and feel good about myself.
再跟这些人 共聚一堂 而不觉得不安
Ooh-oh! Someone's wearing the same clothes they had on last night. Someone get a little action?
有人还穿着昨天晚上的衣服耶 有人有什么艳遇吗？
- I may have. - Woo-hoo,stuud!
或许吧 种马
- What's she look like? - Well,we haven't exactly met,
她长得什么样？ 我们还没见过面呢
we just stayed up all night talking on the internet.
只是在网路上谈了一整夜而已
Woo-hoo,geeek!
驴蛋
I like this girl,okay, I seriously like this girl,
我喜欢她，我真的很喜欢她
you now how sometimes I tend get a little defended and quipy...
你们也晓得 有时我会以笑别人来保护自己
- Get out! - Nooo!
少来了… 不会啦…
Well she totally called me on it,okay. She said,'cut it out,get real',
她直接批评我 她说“少来了，正经一点”
and I did.
我照办了
Wow! What's that like?
那是什么样子？
It's like this,
像这样
me,no jokes.
我，不开玩笑
All right,stop it,you're freaking me out.
好了，你吓死我了
Oh,yeah,I don't like you this way.
是呀，我不喜欢你这样
- All right,I'll see you guys later. - Bye,Richard.
好吧，咱们待会儿见了 拜拜，理查 拜拜
Bye sweetie,
拜，甜心
- I love you. - I love you,too.
我爱你 我也爱你
I think my boyfriend ever so dreamy,
我觉得我男朋友好棒哦
I wonder what our wedding's gonna be like.
不知道我们的婚礼 会是什么样子
What are you talking about? What wedding?
你在胡扯什么？什么婚礼？
Come on,like you never talk about that.
少来了，你们从没谈过吗？
Nooo! Never!
从来都没有
I mean,we're living in the moment.
我们只是很珍惜现在的这一刻
God,it is so nice for once to not have to get all hung up on 'Where is this going?'
就这么一次不去想 “将来会怎么样”，真是棒耶
- Afraid to ask him? - Could not be more terrified.
你怕问他吗？ 怕得不能再怕了
Well,I think you should seriously consider the marriage thing,
我认为你应该认真考虑 结婚这件事情
give Rachel another chance to dress up like Princess Bubble Yum.
再给瑞秋一次 扮成口香糖公主的机会
Where's Benny?
班尼在哪里？
There he is!
他在这里？
Where's Benny,
班尼在哪里？
there he is.
他在这里
Awww! You know that's probably why babies learn to talk,
说不定那是宝宝学说话的原因
so they can tell grown ups to cut it out.
好告诉大人们“够了”
Hey,you know I got a question for you. Just a little thing,no pressure.
我有个问题想要问你 只是件小事啦，没有压力的
Okay.
Did you ever,uh,like,think about the future?
你有想到未来吗？
Sure I do.
当然有
Yeah,am I in it?
是吗？有想到我？
Honey,you are it.
亲爱的 你就是我的未来
Oh God,you are about to get sooo lucky.
天啊，你就要有艳福了
Keep talkin'.
继续说
Well,uh,sometimes I think about selling my practice,
有时我会幻想卖掉我的诊所
we could move to France,
我们搬到法国去
make French toast.
做法国吐司
Okay,so,uh,we're in France,
所以… 我们会在法国…
we're making the toast.
…然后…我们会做吐司…
Do you see a little bassinet in the corner?
你的幻想当中 有没有小小的摇篮？
Like a hound?
猎犬吗？
Not a basset,a bassinet.
不是蓝狗 是摇篮
You really need the bassinet?
你真的需要摇篮？
Well,I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog.
宝宝会从狗上面掉下来呀
Do you,uh,do you,do you not see kids in our future.
你没有幻想过我们有小孩吗？
Oh,hey,I love children,
对，我爱小孩
I have children.
我也有小孩
I just don't want to be 70
但我不想人生在我七十岁…
when our kids go off to college, and our lives can finally start.
…孩子上大学时才开始
Look I want you,now.
我现在 就要你
That's Great.
太棒了
You know we don't need to talk about this now.
我们现在不需要谈这个
Really,I mean this is, is so way,way,way,in the future,
真的，我是说 这是好久好久以后的事情
I'm talkin' hovercrafts and apes taking over the planet.
这是猿人接管了 地球以后的事情嘛
Come on,Chandler,I want this part soo much.
来嘛，钱德 我好想要这个角色哦
Just one kiss,I won't tell anyone.
一吻就好，我不会说的
Joey,no means no!
乔伊，不就是不
I'm sorry we,we don't have your sheep.
对不起，我们没有你的羊
Aww,Rach,I think you look cute
阿秋，我觉得好可爱
And you,uh,you,
而你…你…
- you I could eat with a spoon - Get away from me I said no!
我真想咬你一口 离我远一点，我说不了
- Richard buzzed. He's waiting downstairs. - Oh,Richard's here.
理查在楼下等 理查来了？
I should run down say bye to him
我会下去跟他说再见
Bye.
拜拜 祝一切顺利
So how's your date with your cyberchick going.
跟你那个电脑妞进行如何了？
Ooh,hey,what is all that?
那是什么？
Oh,it's a website,it's the,uh,the Guggenheim museum.
网路地址，那是古根海博物馆
See,she likes art,
她喜欢艺术…
and I like funny words.
而我喜欢怪字…
What does she mean by HH?
她说“HH”是什么意思？
It means we're holding hands.
那就表示我们在牵手了
Are you the cutest?
你真是太可爱了
I'm afraid I might just be.
我想你说对了
You know,what I think is so great that you are totally into this person
我觉得这个很棒耶 你这么喜欢这个人…
and yet for all you know she could be like 90 years old,or have two heads,
…可是她可能已经九十岁了 或者是有两个头
or. It could be a guy.
或者可能根本是个男人
Okay,it's not a guy,all right,I know her.
她不是个男的，好吗？ 我知道她不是
It could be like a big giant guy.
她有可能是个大猛汉哦
Man,I got this close to him and Monica kneed me in the back.
老兄，我就差这么一点了 却被摩妮卡从背后偷袭我
What's going on?
怎么了？
We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.
我们正在猜 钱德的女友是不是女的
Oh,well. Just ask her how long she's gonna live.
那就问她会活多久就可以了
Women live longer than men.
女人比男人长寿
How do you not fall down more?
你还真是笨得到家了
Okay,ask her 'What is her current method of birth control?'
问她用什么方法避孕
All right.
好吧
"My husband is sleeping with his secretary."
“我先生跟他的秘书有外遇”
She's married!
她结婚了？
Well at least we know she's a woman.
至少我们知道她是个女的
I can't believe she's married.
我真不敢相信她结婚了
Aw,man I'm sorry.
老兄，真遗撼
This must be very tough for ya,huh.
你心里一定很难受了
So,I read this article in the paper the other day that says you're not supposed to throw rice at weddings,
我那天读到了一篇文章说 不应该在婚礼上丢米庆祝
because when pigeons eat rice it kills them.
因为鸽子吃了会死掉
Oh,that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars.
难怪寿司吧里都看不到鸽子
- See,we're having fun. - Oh,absolutely.
你瞧，我们很开心 是啊
Yeah,you know I'm not even thinking about that thing that we're not going to be thinking about.
你知道，我们不要去想那件事 我根本连想都不想
Neither am I.
我也是
Hi,there. Are you all right?
你还好吗？
Yeah,when I was in the bathroom I saw the window that I crawled out of at my wedding,
我去洗手间的时候，
看到我结婚时爬出去的那扇窗
and God,I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here,you know I shouldn't,
然后我开始想我不该来的
people are going to be looking at me and judging me and, and thinking about the last time.
大家会打量我，评判我 然后就想到上一次的事
Sweetie,it's be gonna okay,all right. It's a wedding,
亲爱的，你不会有事的 这是场婚礼
generally people focus on the bride.
通常大家都会注意新娘子
God I know,you're right.
天啊，我知道你说得对
All rightie,everybody look at me. Good.
好了，大家看着我，很好
All right,its time. Bridesmaids and ushers let's see two lines,thank you.
时间到了，伴娘跟招待 排成两列，谢谢
Okay,I'll see you after the thing.
咱们婚礼后见了
- Okay,good luck - Thank you
祝好运 谢谢
Okay,Okay.
Why the hell didn't you tell me!
你为什么不告诉我啊？
I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do
对不起，我不知道应该怎么做
stand up and shout 'Hey,Rachel,your butt is showing!'
站起来大叫 “瑞秋，你的屁股露出来了”
Oh my God this is sooo humiliating.
天啊，真是丢脸丢到家了
I think the only thing that tops that was,was,
我想唯一比这个还要丢脸的…
was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing the Copa Cabana in front of the entire school.
就是我八年级在全校面前唱 COPACABANA那次了
I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out.
我大概唱没两句就逃之夭夭了
Oh my God,my entire life is flashing before my eyes.
天啊，我悲惨的一天再现眼前
Rach,hey look,I remember that,it wasn't so bad.
阿秋，听着 我记得没那么糟的
Oh Ross,would you stop, you got me, I'm dating you.
罗斯，你不用说好听话给我听 你已经追到我了
Rachel!
Oh hi,Mr. Wineburg,hi Mrs. Wineburg.
魏先生，魏太太，你好
It's so wonderful to see you again,my dear,
很高兴又看到你了，亲爱的
in fact I hardly expected to see so much.
老实说 我没想到会看到那么多
You told me you didn't see anything.
你说你什么都没看到的
I tell ya a lot things!
我说过很多话
Well it's wonderful to have you up and about,again,dear.
真高兴又看到你出来走动了 亲爱的
Stay well.
好好保重
Okay,now that is the third time someone has said something like that to me today.
类似刚刚那种话 我今天已经听到三次了
Rach! Rach!
阿秋…
- Oh my God,I'm married! - I know.
天啊，我结婚了… 我知道
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter hyphen Farber.
我是方贝利太太了
Oh honey,I'm so proud of you,Min.
我好以你为傲，明蒂
Min.
明蒂
Oh Rach,you're still here,
阿秋，你还在
at our wedding,they were packing up the chopped liver about now.
我们婚礼的这个时候 他们已经在收碗盘了
Yeah,I love that story.
是呀，我爱那个故事
Um,I got a question for you guys.
我有个问题要问你们
Why do people keep is saying that is good to see me up and about?
为什么大家一直说 高兴看到我出来走动？
Well uh,after you ran out on your wedding,
在你逃婚之后…
Barry's parents told people that you were sort of....insane.
…贝利的父母告诉大家说 说你疯了
Insane!
疯了？
...from the syphilis.
梅毒引起的
What?!
什么？
Yeah,what are they gonna say you didn't love me anymore. Come on.
那我该说什么？ 你不再爱我了，少来了
Angela? Joey Tribiani.
安琪？ 我是乔伊
Listen,what are ya doing tonight?
你今晚做什么？
I know your seeing that guy, I was thinking maybe you could bring him.....
我知道你在跟他交往 我在想或许你可以带他来…
Hello? Hello?
Aren't you gonna answer her, that's like the tenth bing-bong message she sent.
你还不回答她吗？ 她已经放了十次话过来了
- She wants to know what's wrong? - What's wrong? What's wrong?
她想知道怎么了
You're married that's what's wrong.
怎么了？ 你结婚了 就是这回事！
- Oh,my. - What?
天啊
She wants to meet you in person.
她想要跟你见面
Hey,look,Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too,
菲比，你听我说 我也想见见她本人
okay,but she's married,she has a husband.
但她结过婚了，她有一个丈夫
What if the husband person is the wrong guy,and you are the right guy.
如果这个丈夫不适合她呢？ 你才适合她呢？
I mean you don't get chances like this all the time,
这种机会不是常有的
if you don't meet her now, you're gonna be kicking yourself
如果你现在不见她，八十岁时 会气得踢自己的屁股…
when your 80,which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.
…这个动作很难 而且会摔断髋骨
Okay,I'll do it!
好吧，我见她
Oh,yeah! Okay! Great!
太棒了
Go,man,go put on your shoes,and,and march out there and meet her!
穿上鞋子然后走出去见见她
Oh,wait,no,no you have to take a shower,'cause,eww.
老天，不，等等… 你必须先洗个热水澡…
No,you know what you have to answer her,answer her first.
不，先回答她的问题
No,no,you know what make some coffee 'cause its too much.
不…你…你先煮咖啡 因为太大压力了
Okay,one more,please. Come on, I'm gonna get it in this time,I will.
好了，拜托再一次嘛 我这次会丢进去的
Okay,last chance.
好吧，最后一次
Again,I'm sorry.
对不起，又打到你了
You know what,maybe I don't need to have children.
知道吗？ 或许我不需要有孩子
You know maybe I just think I do because that is what society,
或许我只是以为我需要 因为那是一种社会…
and by that I mean my mom,
…我是指我妈啦…
has always convinced me that I...
…她一直让我相信我…
I do,
需要
I have to have children,I'm sorry. I just do.
我必须要有小孩，对不起 我必须要
Yo! Can I have your attention,please,
请大家注意
Best Man,making a toast here.
伴O要敬酒了
Thank you.
谢谢
I remember when Barry got home from his first date with Rachel...
我记得贝利第一次 跟瑞秋约会回来的时候
What?!
什么？
What,you hired the same band I can't use the same speech.
你没有换乐队 却要我换演讲稿吗？
Thank you,thank you very much.
谢谢，非常谢谢
Anyway,I wish you both a wonderful life together.
反正，希望你们从此过着幸福快乐的日子
And Rachel...
还有瑞秋
- What. - No,no,no now in all seriousness,
什么？ 不…我很认真的
its not a lot of women would've had the guts to come back here tonight,
没有多少女人有这个胆子 在今天晚上回来这里
and even fewer, who would do it with their asses hanging out!
而且还敢露小屁股回来的 那就更少了
Uh,I like to,uh,to add something to that...
我想加上几句话
- Why are you adding,why are you adding,why are you adding,why are you adding?
你要加什么？…
Most of you don't know me,I'm Rachel's boyfriend.
你们大半都不认识我 我是瑞秋的男朋友…
Oh dear God.
老天
Ross,
…我叫罗斯
uh and uh,I'd just like to say that it did take a lot of courage for Rachel to come here tonight.
我想说 瑞秋真的是鼓足了勇气 在今天晚上回到这里来的
And,uh,for the record
而且呢 我想澄清…
she did not run out on Barry because she had syphilis.
…瑞秋并不是 因为得了梅毒才逃婚的
What are you doing I'm serious.
我这是认真的
Uh,the reason she walked out on,on Barry is simply that she didn't love him,
她离开贝利的原因 其实很简单 她并不爱他
which incidentally worked out pretty well for me
所以呢，那就成就了我的美事
Cheers!
干杯
- See you in the parking lot. - No,Rach!
咱们停车场见 阿秋
And once again she is out of here.
她又再一次离开了
Okay who had 9:45? Um?
谁赌9点45分？
Ya,know what Barr,I'm not gonna leave.
你知道吗，贝利？ 我不想走了
I probably should,but I'm not,
我大概应该走，但是我不走
see 'cause I promised myself that I would make it through at least *one* of your weddings.
因为我答应我自己 至少要过完一次你的婚礼
See now,tonight,all I really wanted was
我今天真正想要的只不过是…
to make it though this evening with a little bit of grace and dignity.
一点优雅跟尊严来度过今晚
Well,I guess we can all agree that's not gonna happen.
我猜我们都同意 那是不可能的了
There's nothing really left to say except....
我猜也没什么好说的了 除了…
"Her name was Lola. She was a showgirl.
她叫做萝拉 是个歌舞女O
With yellow feathers,feathers in her hair,and a dress cut down to there.
头上插着 黄色羽毛 还穿着性感小洋装
She would..."
她…
- Marenge,- "...marenge,thank you honey,
会热舞 会热舞，谢谢你，甜心
and do the cha-cha.
还会跳恰恰
And while she like to be a star,Tony always tended bar.
她喜欢当明星的滋味 而东尼则是酒保
At the,wait,wait,everybody.."
在… 等等… 大家一起来！
柯帕 柯帕柯巴拿
是哈瓦那最带劲的地方
在柯帕
柯帕柯巴拿
那里音乐热情不辍
Okay,I'll do it.
好吧，我愿意
You'll do what?
你愿意什么？
If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.
如果在一起必须有孩子 那就有吧
Oh my God!
天啊
If I have to I'll,I'll do all again,
有必要的话，我就再来一次
I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing,
我会四点起来喂奶
I'll go to the P.T.A. meetings,
我会参加父母师长会
I'll coach the soccer team.
当足球队的教练
- Really? - Yeah,if I have to.
真的？ 对，有必要的话
Monica,
摩妮卡…
I don't wanna lose you,
…我不想失去你
so if I have to do it all over again, then I will.
所以如果我得重来一次 我还是会的
You're the most wonderful man.
你真是我遇见过最棒的男人
And if you hadn't of said 'if I have to' like seventeen times,
如果你没说那么多“必须”的话
then I'd be saying 'okay,let's do it.'
…那么我会说 “好吧，咱们生吧”
But you're not.
但是你不会
Oh my God,
天啊
I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say.
真不敢相信我就要这么说了
I wanna have a baby,
我想要一个孩子
but I don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.
但我不想跟一个 并不是真的想孩子的人一起生
God.
天啊
I love you.
我爱你
I know you do.
我知道
Me too.
我也是
So what now?
现在呢？
I guess we just
现在我们就只有…
keep dancing.
…一直跳下去
Where is she,Where is she?
她在哪里？…
Oh,hey,I have a question,where is she?
我有个问题 她在哪里？
Chandler,relax,Chandler,she'll be here.
钱德，你放心吧 她会来的
Ooh,oh,oh,that's her.
她来了
Yeah,'cause life's just that kind.
对，因为人生真美好
Chandler,you gotta stop staring at the door. It's like a watched pot,
钱德，你得停止盯着门看 那就像你在等水滚
you know if you keep looking at it then the door is to, never gonna boil.
如果你一直盯着不放的话 那扇门就永远不会开的
I think what you have to do is try not to...
我认为你必须试着不去…
Oh my God!
老天啊
OH.....MY.....GAWD!!
我的…老…天啊
OH.....MY.....GOD!!
All right I've been feeling incredibly guilty about this,
好吧 我一直觉得好对不起你
because I wanna be a good friend, and dammit I am a good friend. So just,just shut up and close your eyes.
因为我想当个好朋友 该死，我是个好朋友 所以，闭嘴并且闭上眼睛
Wow,you are a good friend,
你真是好朋友
'course the audition was this morning,and I didn't get it.
对了，试镜是今天早上 而我出局了
But that was a hell of a kiss.
但是你吻功真不错
Rachel is a very lucky girl.
瑞秋是个很幸运的女孩